

Mustafa Dishad Graphic designer

Contact

Mustafadlshad01@gmail.com

+964 750 854 22 83

Languages

Kurdish English Arabic

Skills APhotoshop 3ds max Sketch After effect In design

Hobbies

Painting

Reading

Professional Profile:

Expert as a Graphic designer along with 3D and 2D designes with 6 years experience in animation, educational video development, and illustration. and precise in career committeent, competent and reliable. looking for oppurtunities to gain some valuable work, with ability to perform work with creativity.

Experience:

2019-2021 Participated in 3d model development for blender platform online.

2020-2023 Designed few logos for some mini organizations.

2021-2022 Designed medical educational 3D models for the college.

2022-2023 Produced an educational video of the structure of the eye for an organization.

Education and Qualification:

Medical Student at Kirkuk College of Medicine (Stage 5)

Additional skills:

Proficient in Microsoft Office and Adobe Creative Suite

Strong problem-solving and communication skills

Ability to work independently and in a team

Connect:



www.Instargram.com /mustafa_dlshad01



www.behance.com /mustafadlshad1



www.linkedin.com /in/masto-designer-69120326a